Hi.
My name is Jessica Meiczinger with Simply Divine Events, a wedding planner who's been planning weddings for over ten years.
I'm here to talk about how to choose your reception menu for your elegant beach theme wedding.
First of all, I'd stick obviously include your local flavor.
If there's any seafood delicacies that are in the area or just seafood in general, try to have that in your beach themed wedding.
You could do a buffet or station style.
In that, you could do like a raw bar setup on blocks of ice or you can do ice sculpture that's part of a center piece of a buffet with like your seafood adorning that.
But, mainly most of the time for an elegant beach theme wedding you're probably going to do a seated dinner.
For appetizer, of course you could start off with like a lobster bisque or crab cakes and then roll into your salad.
And, then for your entree you could do a surf and turf whether it be steak and shrimp or steak and lobster.
There's just endless possibilities when it comes to choosing your reception menu for your elegant beach theme wedding.